http://www.barges.org/homepage/privacy-a-cookies

DBA
About usJoin usMembership & BenefitsMembers Websites & BlogsContact usRepresentation - UKRepresentation - EUDBA PoliciesRelated OrganisationsWebsite LegibilityPrivacy and Cookies
Adverts
SearchAdvertising in Blue Flag
Forum
Recent TopicsAbout the ForumForum RulesForum Help
KnowledgeBase
Buying a bargeSafety on Barges
Body OverboardLife-JacketsFire Extinguishers
Water-Mist Extinguishers
Petrol Generators
TrainingRegulations
The Boat...
Size MattersBoat RegistrationES-TRIN (was TRIWV) Use of Red DieselAISNew-Builds & RCDFranceFrench TVA on bargesUK VAT on bargesWaterway CategoriesENI - European Number
The SkipperVHF RadioAISLinks to Originals
CruisingCommunications
VHF Radio...
Getting a UK ships radio licenceGetting a Dutch Ships VHF Licence
AISSatellite TVInternet and PhoneMobile Internet Best BuysBoosting Internet Access
External
Rust TreatmentBoat Surveys and SurveyorsWheelhouseAnodesNavigation LightsBollardsFlag Weights & Balls
Internal
Water & Fuel TanksWater Filtration SystemsFire ExtinguishersWinterizingConcrete BallastCondensation
Mechanical
Oil or Diesel in the BilgeULS & Bio DieselGTL DieselDiesel BugDAF EnginesSmoky DAFsBow ThrustersAntifreezeStern Gland Stuffing
STOPPAGES !Electrical
Lead-Acid BatteriesGel or AGMLithium-ion vs AGMSolar ElectricsGalvanic IsolationNavigation LightsAnodes
Library
About the LibraryDBA CalendarDBA ConstitutionBlue Flag MagazineeNewsletters
Publications
Barge Buyer's HandbookGuide to Barge Handling'Blue Flag'
Blue Flag Sample copies
Advertising in Blue FlageNewslettersDBA Calendar
EventsLogin/out
Trouble Logging in?Passord resetForgotten Username
HomePrivacy and Cookies
DBA is committed to protecting the privacy of members and visitors to the site
Some of the DBA site can be viewed by guests without DBA receiving any information about you. However, for members to access the site  DBA needs to receive certain information before that access can be provided. The following policy explains how and why we collect information, and how that information will be used. This policy covers the treatment of both anonymous and personally identifiable information that may be collected when you visit and request services from the DBA website.
Information Collection and Use
Anonymous information is collected on visitors to the website by the log files. This information is for statistical purposes only and includes information such as IP addresses, types of browsers used, referring/exit pages, platform type, tracking of movements to analyze trends, and provides broad geographical and demographic information. The information collected is not linked to any personally identifiable information.
Information Sharing
When you use Enquiries and Feedback, we ask for your name, address and contact details so that you can be sent a response to your query or feedback. By using the DBA website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by DBA. DBA will not share any personally identifiable information with third parties.
Access to View, Edit & Delete Personally Identifiable Information
You may request to view, edit or delete any personally identifiable information that  DBA holds about you. This information will be held on  our membership database for up to three months after  your subscription is not received. Then it will be archived.  If you wish to have your information deleted DBA will remove any personally identifiable tags, but it may be archived for statistical use. Credit card information is never stored.
Members data
The data we hold about DBA members and the uses to which it is put are explained at the foot of this article
External Links
This website contains links to other sites.  DBA is not responsible for the privacy policies of such sites. This privacy policy applies solely to the collection of information from this site, barges.org.
Cookies
The website currently uses browser cookies to enhance use of the site. This may be subject to change in the future. Notification of such a change will be dealt with in accordance to the practice set out in the Changes to Policy section below.
Email from DBA
Email will occasionally be sent to members, manually or automatically.
•  Our website sends automatic emails only to remind you that your subscription needs renewing and these cannot be stopped while you are a member but you should only get one each year.
•  DBA membership administrators will occasionally send out emails to all or groups of members relating to information that is essential to the running of the association, e,g. your opportunity to vote online for AGM matters.
You can choose to receive or stop other emails from us, in My Details, on the website Members menu
•   Blue Flag:  A link to a new issue will be emailed to you only if you have chosen eBF .
•  The eNewsletter:  will be emailed to you on alternate months if you have chosen it.
•  Other emails may occasionally be sent to you only if you have chosen them in My Details.
•  Forum postings: Use the Subscribe and Unsubscribe buttons on the Forum topics. Read the Forum Help page for more information
•  Classified adverts, change the tick boxes in your profile at Members/My Details on the website menu, to request or stop alerts. If you have placed an advert you will be sent any enquiries until the advert expires or you delete it.
•  Barge Register: If you have chosen to allow other members to contact you in a Barge Register entry, you may recieve emails rom other members and can switch it off by updating your entry.
Contact from Other DBA Members
•  The  Member Finder  facility allows you to let other members contact you by email, phone or PM*, according to your settings in My Details.
•   If you post on the Forum,  other members may contact you by PM
•   If you put your barge on the Barge Register, you can choose to allow other members to contact you by PM.
•  If you place an advert  you will need to give some contact details to allow a buyer to respond to the advert
•  If you add your Website or Blog you may provide contact details.
*  The Private Messaging (PM) facility in the website allows members to contact each other, without revealing any email addresses.  You will be notified of the PM by email but will need to log on to the Forum to reply.  It is useful to make an introduction before choosing (or not) to start an email or phone conversation.
Post
You will receive Blue Flag magazine by post if you have chosen to (in My Details).
We will only contact you by post otherwise if we have no valid email address for you AND need to contact you about your membership.
Changes to This Policy
DBA may amend this policy from time to time. If there is any substantial change to the way that the personally identifiable information is handled, this will be announced on the website and in Blue Flag.
Questions or Comments
If you have any further questions, or would like to comment on the Privacy Policy or any other aspect of the DBA website, please contact us.
Members data
1)  Data we hold about all members
Name
Postal Address
eMail address
Phone number(s)
Your barge-ownership status
2) Data we only hold if you have volunteered it
Details of your barge
Your main cruising country
The URL of your Blog or Website
Items you have added to the Adverts section of the website
3) What we do with your data
All data under (1) is used only for membership administration, posting Blue Flag and emailing  items you have chosen above (see eMail).
Details of your barge are available only to other members in the Barge register
Your Blog or Website address is available to the public.
Your Adverts are visible to the public.  Your email address is not visible.
4) Deletion of your data
If you cease to be a member, your personal data, as above, will be deleted
You can delete or change your personal data at any time in 'My Details' or by request to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Print
Email
Login/out (2)Trouble Logging in? DBA (2)About DBAJoin!Membership BenefitsSubscriptionsApplication formContactsMembers WebsitesRepresentation - UKRepresentation - EURelated OrganisationsWebsite LegibilityPrivacy and CookiesMembers (2)ShopMembers WebsitesTrouble Logging in?Join DBAMembership BenefitsSubscriptionsAdverts (2)Forum (2)Recent TopicsAbout the ForumForum RulesForum HelpKnowledgeBase (2)Buying a bargeWhat is a Barge?Where can I cruise?Where can I Moor?How do I Buy?New Boat or Old?How do I learn more?Selling a BargeTrainingTraining schoolsSafety on BargesLife-JacketsPetrol GeneratorsFire ExtinguishersWater-Mist ExtinguishersBody OverboardRegulationsThe Boat...Size MattersBoat RegistrationES-TRIN (was TRIWV) Use of Red DieselUK VAT on bargesAISFranceWaterway CategoriesNew-Builds & RCDFrench TVA on bargesVHF RadioThe SkipperLinks to OriginalsAISCommunicationsInternet and PhoneVHF Radio...Getting a Dutch Ships VHF LicenceGetting a UK ships radio licenceMobile Internet Best BuysAISBoosting Internet AccessSatellite TVInternalWater & Fuel TanksWater Filtration SystemsFire ExtinguishersWinterizingRepacking a Stern GlandConcrete BallastCondensationExternalRust TreatmentWheelhouseAnodesBoat Surveys and SurveyorsNavigation LightsBollardsMechanicalStern Gland StuffingOil or Diesel in the BilgeULS & Bio DieselDAF EnginesBow ThrustersAntifreezeSmoky DAFsDiesel BugElectricalLead-Acid BatteriesGalvanic IsolationSolar ElectricsLithium-ion vs AGMNavigation LightsGel or AGMCruisingCruising in...BelgiumFranceGermanyIrelandNetherlandsUKThe German DanubeThe French Rhine - Charges ComparedTaking a barge to Sea! STOPPAGES !Tunnels!FlagsBooks and ChartsCrossing the ChannelLiving in...BelgiumNetherlandsSTOPPAGES !Satellite TV
